The Lucky One is a drama, romance film directed by Scott Hicks.
A Marine travels to Louisiana after serving three tours in Iraq and searches for the
unknown woman he believes was his good luck charm during the war.
Logan Thibault, played by Zac Efron.
Beth Clayton, played by Taylor Schilling.
Nana, played by Blythe Danner.
Keith Clayton, played by Jay R. Ferguson.
Ben Clayton, played by Riley Thomas Stewart.
Deputy Moore, played by Joe Chrest.
The Lucky One is a 2012 American romantic drama film directed
by Scott Hicks and released in April 2012.
It is an adaptation of Nicholas Sparks’ 2008 novel of the same name.
The film stars Zac Efron as Logan Thibault, a US Marine who finds a photograph of a young woman while serving in Iraq,
carries it around as a good luck charm, and later tracks down the woman, with whom he begins a relationship.
The film received negative reviews but grossed over $99.4 million.
The film explores themes of husband wife relationship, based on
novel or book, iraq war veteran, photo, kennel.
The tone is emotional.